<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Yandex Browser | Aleksandr Filatov]]></title>
  <link href="http://alfilatov.com/blog/categories/yandex-browser/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://alfilatov.com/"/>
  <updated>2015-05-12T12:12:04+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://alfilatov.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aleksandr Filatov]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yandex Browser? It's Need or Not?]]></title>
    <link href="http://alfilatov.com/blog/2012/12/13/yandex-browser-it-need-or-not/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://alfilatov.com/blog/2012/12/13/yandex-browser-it-need-or-not</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yandex.Browser with a full set of features designed specifically for the English-speaking users will be released soon. (с)
<img src="http://yabs.yandex.ru/count/AI9QGHYaezm40002Zhqbnmm5KPK2cmPfMeYosr1G0vAjXGQgfZIAe4K6Kge2fPOOP92W7mBUaRpGIMG6an11hlnExYmQdEFG1B41VmS0" alt="yandex_browser_logo" />
Not so early, Yandex company on yours conference is <a href="http://fotki.yandex.ru/users/ya-events/album/136128/">YaC 2012</a> presented the <a href="http://browser.yandex.com/">Yandex browser 1.0</a>. Let&rsquo;s show it inside.</p>

<p>The engine of this thing is open source browser <code>Chromium</code>. Some intresting, that Some sites detected that it&rsquo;s 19 version of google chrome, but at the moment of this post <code>Google Chrome</code> has 23.xxx version. String of search find in Yandex on default. So, already we have some Google and some Yandex. &ldquo;Yeah.. Not enough Opera&rdquo; - thinking guys from Yandex and added Turbo technology by Opera. It&rsquo;s mix equals to Yandex browser. Some people have a nick &ldquo;Stringy&rdquo; for the specific logo.</p>

<p>And we can see a mix of modern technology. Therefore, on my mind it&rsquo;s &ldquo;discovered bicycle&rdquo; (it is russian flying phrase). At the first time, we can&rsquo;t see new many features. Of all proposed <a href="http://browser.yandex.com/">here</a>, I would single out only the following:</p>

<ul>
<li>New view of URL. Now url will not so lenght. It&rsquo;s will be name of web page look like bread crumbs</li>
<li>New menu of fast link - &ldquo;Tableu&rdquo;. Favorite sites will only be a click away and colorful widgets will show you up-to-date information about the weather and traffic, as well as social network notifications.</li>
<li>Smartbox - Enter your searches and websites into the Smartbox. Search suggestions will help you search more quickly and autocorrect errors.</li>
</ul>


<p>And so on, I think that guys from Yandex must have hard working on th</span>is thing, and may be some version their have a fortune.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
