<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Contributon | Aleksandr Filatov]]></title>
  <link href="http://alfilatov.com/blog/categories/contributon/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://alfilatov.com/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-10T12:45:36+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://alfilatov.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aleksandr Filatov]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Contribution in Mozilla Society]]></title>
    <link href="http://alfilatov.com/blog/2012/12/10/my-contribution-in-mozilla-society/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://alfilatov.com/blog/2012/12/10/my-contribution-in-mozilla-society</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&rsquo;s my first publication on english. And it&rsquo;s blog some training for my english. And so on, in this topic I&rsquo;d like to tell about Mozilla society. And how I become in mozilla contribution list. For me it&rsquo;s very intresting to participate in some activities. But I&rsquo;m not a mozilla evangelist. :)</p>

<p>I think that not secret for each other that mozilla it&rsquo;s global web society where each people can have yours contribution: programming, design sites, translate article on <a href="https://developer.mozilla.org/ru/">mozilla network</a></p>

<p>Site <a href="http://whatcanidoformozilla.org/">what can I do for mozilla</a> help a new people who it&rsquo;s can intrested. If you like makes open source world better, that it&rsquo;s makes interested you. Some of yours can see page with title &ldquo;Our Contributors&rdquo; on menu &ldquo;About Firefox&rdquo; - &ldquo;global society&rdquo; in mozilla products. Perhaps you too would become on this page. It&rsquo;s very easy. There are some advice after this.</p>

<h3>What I can do?</h3>

<p>Translate to russian some topics on <a href="https://developer.mozilla.org/ru/">mozilla network</a> or other resource of this society. If you are developer you can started for fix some minor bugs for Firefox, Thunderbird, and etc. After your &nbsp;review code you can get access to repository with more content. If you think that you makes some good things for society you can send letter to <code>credits@mozilla.org</code> giving your name, email address and a sentence (citation) summarizing your contribution. If it&rsquo;s true you have a lot of chance be on board contribution. And have&nbsp;mental pleasure :)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
